easyduplicatefinder.com 2017-05-07

# Easy Duplicate Finder™ - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY NOTICE

WebMinds, Inc. has been awarded DL Shield's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by DL Shield for compliance with DL Shield's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  DL Shield's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at support@webminds.com.  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact DL Shield here. The DL Shield program covers only information that is collected through the English version of this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site, or translated versions of the site.

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for site’s owned by WebMinds, Inc. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

#### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

In order to use our service, we collect certain personal information from you. We collect contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number;   
As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.  These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We do not sell, rent or otherwise share your personal information with any third parties.    

As part of our service, WebMinds, Inc. collects the email addresses of senders and recipients for the purpose of delivering files.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if WebMinds, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets,  you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

#### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies & persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. 

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once.  Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.    
If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

**Tracking Technologies & Third Party Cookies**

The use of cookies by our partners & affiliates is not covered by our privacy statement.  We /do not have access or control over these cookies. 

We use Google Analytics, a third-party tracking service, which uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about our visitors to our site in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics. Some of our business partners (e.g., Google Analytics) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

#### Web beacons 

Our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.  
We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

#### Links to Other Web Sites 

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of WebMinds, Inc. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

#### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website, or at support@webminds.com:

\- See what data we have about you, if any.  
\- Change/correct any data we have about you.  
\- Have us delete any data we have about you.  
\- Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

#### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

#### Additional Policy Information

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it. 

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs & community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at support@webminds.com.

You can link to our site using social networking services such as Facebook & Twitter. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your sign-in information, name and email address to link between the sites. Services like Facebook & Twitter give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

In your account, you can import contacts from your Outlook or other email account address book to make it easier to use our service. Information must first be exported from Outlook or other email account address book in a text or CSV format. Only then can the information be imported into your account. We never connect directly to any third party application to collect information. Any contact information must be imported in a standard separated format.  . 

You may also send your contacts an invite them to become members of our site . 

#### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes 

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### Use of Information

WebMinds may use Information collected in connection with the Site in the following ways:

  * To provide requested information, products and services to users
  * To improve the user experience with the Site
  * In connection with the operation of the Site and WebMind's internal business
  * In connection with other Sites or offline businesses owned or operated by WebMinds
  * For Users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by WebMinds as well as selected third parties.

#### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

WebMinds, Inc.  
8540 Dayton Avenue  
Fort Myers, FL 33907
